sbimf.com 2016-08-01

# SBI MF - Privacy Policy

Welcome to the website/mobile application of the SBI Mutual Fund. We understand that our customers and website/mobile application visitors are concerned about the privacy of information. We have established policies and procedures concerning the collection, use and security of your information that will help protect your privacy. Our privacy policies are designed to help us serve our customers while maintaining strict privacy and security standards. 

At SBI Mutual Fund, we recognize the importance of keeping the information we collect about you confidential. That is why we have always taken great care to protect your information. Changes to our privacy policies may be made occasionally. We recommend that visitors to our site and mobile application users review our privacy policies from time to time to learn of new privacy practices and changes to our policies. 

We may collect information about you from several sources. You may provide information as part of the application or enrollment process or our landing pages during online campaigns. Additionally we may obtain information about you from third parties. We also develop and retain information about you based on our transactions and experience with you. Finally, we obtain information about you through Internet technology, including our website/mobile application. 

**Security Standards and measures**

We adopt reasonable security practices and procedures and will protect your Personal Information by reasonable security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the Personal Information, consistent with generally accepted standards of commercial business practice, which includes, technical, operational, managerial and physical security controls in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, or disclosure while it is under our control. 

You agree and understand that when we use trusted third parties to act on our behalf for performing certain functions such as processing transactions, issuing account statements, payment gateway services, customer services etc., contractual or other means are used to ensure reasonable security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the Personal Information, consistent with generally accepted standards of commercial business practice. 

Any account statement containing financial information pertaining to the investor, if it is to be sent over the internet to such investor, distributors or any other entity as indicated above will be sent only through a secure means and/or through encrypted electronic mail. 

You may download materials, data etc displayed on the website for non-commercial and/or personal use only. You may not, however, distribute, modify, transmit, reuse, report, or use the contents of the website for public or commercial purposes, including the text, images, audio and video without SBI Mutual Fund’s written permission. 

You shall not delete, modify and/or otherwise interfere with copyright or other intellectual property rights displayed on the website. 

**Online Information Collection**

For each visitor to our website/mobile application, our Web server automatically recognizes the visitor's Internet service provider. Additionally, we collect information about the sites visitors connect from, and the browsers visitors use. We use this information to assemble aggregate information about the visitors to our website/mobile application, and assist with our systems administration and problem resolution activities. 

We collect personally identifiable information in order to identify and register a SBI Mutual Fund investor. The information we collect will vary depending upon the function you select. For example you may be required to provide information such as: 

| 

Name 

|  | 

Account Information 

|    
---|---|---|---|---  
| 

Address 

|  | 

PAN Number 

|    
| 

Birthday 

|  | 

Folio No. 

|    
| 

Phone number 

|   |   |    
  
If you supply us with your e-mail address on-line you may receive periodic messages from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you supply us with your telephone number on-line you may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding products or services you have or asked about on-line. You also may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. 

SBI Mutual Fund makes no representations of any kind whatsoever about the content of any such web site that you may access through this website. You are advised to read the terms and conditions/disclaimers of such website that may be accessed by you. SBI Mutual Fund also advises you to confirm the accuracy of any such information before seeking to rely on such information. SBI Mutual Fund disclaims all liability that you may incur as a result of relying on any such reports/information and/or accessing any other website and/or any third party content that may be accessed from the website. 

  **Visitor Data Collected on this Website/mobile application**

 The information for the accounts you have with the SBI Mutual Fund website/mobile application is kept secure and confidential through multiple security features and procedures. The information you request from our website/mobile application for your accounts can only be accessed with your password. It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not disclose your password to anyone. Our employees and associates will never ask you for your password. Never write your password on something others may see. Contact us immediately to change your password if you suspect someone has discovered it. Information you submit through our website/mobile application, as well as the information we send back to you while you are visiting our website/mobile application, is protected while passing through the Internet using strong encryption ("scrambling" to make it incomprehensible) when necessary. Our secure server software encrypts information, ensuring that Internet communications through our website/mobile application stay private and protected. To enable our customers to process transactions at our website/mobile application, we use cookies. 

Your account information is not permanently stored on our Web server. The information only resides on our Web server while you are viewing the information. It is permanently stored on our secured corporate computer systems. Our corporate network systems, which store your account information, use proven security controls. We have data security staff whose sole responsibilities are to ensure the security of the information we process and store. 

SBI Mutual Fund has policies and procedures in place to limit access to your information to only those who have a business need to view it. 

  **Use of Cookies**

The www.sbimf.com site, like many web sites, uses "cookies" (information stored on your computer by your browser at our request). Cookies enable the site to "remember" who you are so that you can get around it easier and more efficiently. Cookies allow you to access secured information, conduct secured transactions, and take advantage of promotional opportunities. 

Different web sites store the information in cookies differently. We do not record personal or sensitive information in our cookies. Any such information is stored in our protected systems and not in the cookie or on the Internet. 

 This policy describes how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Web site / mobile application. 

 If you visit our site / mobile application to read or download information, we may collect and/or store the following information about you: 

  * the name of the domain from which you access the Internet ;
  * the date and time you accessed our site/ mobile application;
  * the Internet address of the Web site / mobile application from which you linked directly to our site;
  * the page locations where you visited, and other miscellaneous site references.

Some pages on this Web site employ "cookies." A cookie is a small file that a Web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk to allow the server to "remember" specific information about your session while you are connected. SBI Mutual Fund may find it necessary to use the "cookies" system to collect data when you visit our web pages / mobile application. This will help us find out which sections of our pages you are interested in.

Requests to send cookies are not designed to collect information about you, but only about your "browser session." The cookies make it easier for you to use the dynamic features of our Web site / mobile application. The cookies and the information about your session are automatically destroyed shortly after you close your browser. The information is not permanently stored on your computer. No personal information about you is collected except as described above.

The primary reason for doing this is to enable SBI Mutual Fund to appreciate, better, your centres of interest and send you information specific to your requirements. Such data will not be held for more than one year. 

This website / mobile application does not collect any personal information that identifies a visitor to this site/ mobile application individually unless specified otherwise. Your visit to this site / mobile application will record only the Domain Name Server part of your e-mail address and of the pages visited within this website / mobile application. The information we receive depends upon what you do when visiting our site. This information is used for management and enhancement of our Web site / mobile application and also to prepare aggregate information about the visitors to the site and statistics on usage patterns.

If you identify yourself by sending an e-mail or ordering forms/brochures, we will only use this information to respond to your request and improve our Customer Services. Names and addresses are kept in our Customer Services system for 3 months in order to follow up on orders if necessary. They are then deleted from the system.

While every care has been taken in preparing the information and materials contained in this site, such information and materials are provided to you "as is" without warranty of any kind either express or implied. SBI Mutual Fund does not warranty the adequacy of the information made available. In particular, no warranty regarding non-infringement, security, accuracy, fitness for a particular purpose or freedom from computer virus is given in conjunction with such information and materials.

**Cookies**

"Cookies" will also save you from having to supply information that you have previously given, every time you connect. It will be possible for you to detect these "cookies" and, if you wish, delete them. 

To do this, we would remind you that your web browser software contains the option of blocking "cookies" on your computer: .

  * If your web browser is Internet Explorer 3 or 4 (Microsoft): Click on "display", "options", "advanced". Among the various displays you could call up, the fourth is entitled "prompt before accepting cookies" and, on Internet Explorer 4 only, the fifth is entitled "always refuse cookies". 
  * If your web browser is Internet Explorer 5 (Microsoft): Click on "tools", " internet options ", "security", "custom level". Under the "cookies" heading, select "prompt" or "disable" against the proposed options. 
  * If your web browser is Navigator Gold 3 (Netscape): Click on "options", "network preferences", "protocols". Among the various prompts that you can activate, the first is entitled "prompt before accepting a cookie". You will then be prompted when a "cookie" arrives and you can have it refused by your browser software. 
  * If your web browser is Communicator (Netscape): Click on "edit", "preferences" and highlight "advanced". Select the required option. 

****

**Other web connections: hypertext links**

****

Our web pages / mobile application also offer links to other sites for which we are not responsible either for their standards of public order and decency, or for their personal data protection policy or the use that could be made of such data.

When you access another website through a hypertext link, you are accepting that this access is at your own risk. Consequently, SBI Mutual Fund cannot accept responsibility for any direct or indirect damages that may result from your access to another site connected by a hypertext link.

We would also draw your attention to the use of public forums where you may be asked to give your identity or e-mail address. This information then enters the public domain and may be used by a third party using the service.

****

**Breach of Internet Security**

****

Despite our best efforts, if unauthorized persons breach our security control measures resulting in the Site being hacked or presenting inaccurate information etc., SBI Mutual Fund, SBI Funds Management Private Limited, SBI Mutual Fund Trustee Company Private Limited, their directors, officers, employees or affiliates’ will not be responsible.

Unless otherwise stated, we own the intellectual property rights in the website / mobile application and material on the website / mobile application. You may view, download for caching purposes only, and print pages from the website / mobile application for your own personal use, subject to the restrictions set out in these terms and conditions of use.

****

Top

****
